

CONTACT

- 09610298605
- rochenettel@gmail.com
- Alegria, Cebu

SKILLS

- Figma
- Substance painter
- Quixel Bridge
- Word
- Excel

ROCHENETTE LEGASPINA

UI/UX Designer



PROFILE

I am a highly motivated UI/UX Designer committed to continuous learning and self-improvement. With a strong work ethic and passion for design, I focus on creating user-centered experiences while refining my skills. My diverse experience as a System Analyst, UI/UX Designer, and 3D Modeler has strengthened my technical proficiency and problem-solving abilities, enabling me to excel in the design field.



EDUCATION

University of Cebu

Bachelor of Science in Computer Engineering 2016-2021



WORK EXPERIENCE

System Analyst & UI/UX Designer

Alliance Software Inc. 2023 - Present

UI/UX Designer

Mach95 Software Development Corporation 2021-2022

3D Modeler & Substance Painter Designer

Exodia Game Development Outsourcing 2019-2021

Contributed to the CASA GORORDO MUSEUM VR project as a 3D Modeller